export const chapter = "Chapter - 9: Determiner";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "What is the function of a determiner in a sentence?",
          optionA: "To express actions",
          optionB: "To modify a noun",
          optionC: "To connect clauses",
          correctAnswer: "B) To modify a noun",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is an example of a Demonstrative Determiner?",
          optionA: "Some",
          optionB: "This",
          optionC: "Much",
          correctAnswer: "B) This",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Identify the Interrogative Determiner in the sentence: 'Which shirt is mine?'",
          optionA: "What",
          optionB: "Which",
          optionC: "Whose",
          correctAnswer: "B) Which",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What category do words like 'my,' 'your,' and 'its' fall into?",
          optionA: "Demonstrative Determiners",
          optionB: "Interrogative Determiners",
          optionC: "Possessive Determiners",
          correctAnswer: "C) Possessive Determiners",
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following is a Numeral Determiner?",
          optionA: "Much",
          optionB: "Several",
          optionC: "Little",
          correctAnswer: "B) Several",
        },
        {
          question: "When is the Indefinite Article 'A' used?",
          optionA: "Before a noun starting with a vowel sound",
          optionB: "Before a noun starting with a consonant sound",
          optionC: "Before any noun",
          correctAnswer: "B) Before a noun starting with a consonant sound",
        },
        {
          question: "In what situations is the Definite Article 'The' used?",
          optionA: "Only before proper nouns",
          optionB: "Only before abstract nouns",
          optionC: "Before specific or particular nouns",
          correctAnswer: "C) Before specific or particular nouns",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is a case where Articles are omitted?",
          optionA: "Before names of days and months",
          optionB: "Before names of games",
          optionC: "Before possessive determiners",
          correctAnswer: "B) Before names of games",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which sentence demonstrates the correct use of the Definite Article before a class of nouns?",
          optionA: "'A dog is a faithful animal.'",
          optionB: "'The gentle are sure to win others' hearts.'",
          optionC: "'I can give you my car if you allow my truck to go.'",
          correctAnswer: "B) 'The gentle are sure to win others' hearts.'",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In which scenario should Articles be omitted according to the text?",
          optionA: "Before names of languages",
          optionB: "Before names of books and newspapers",
          optionC: "Before proper nouns like Mount Everest",
          correctAnswer: "C) Before proper nouns like Mount Everest",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blanks:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "This classification was based on __________.",
          optionA: "Wealth",
          optionB: "Family lineage",
          optionC: "Occupations",
          correctAnswer: "Occupations",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The son of a Brahmin became a priest while that of a carpenter became __________ else but a carpenter.",
          optionA: "A scholar",
          optionB: "A trader",
          optionC: "None",
          correctAnswer: "None",
        },
        {
          question:
            "A low-caste scholar was not allowed to __________ and teach.",
          optionA: "Travel",
          optionB: "Study",
          optionC: "Farm",
          correctAnswer: "Study",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Those engaged in 'dirty' or 'lowly' occupations were termed 'low-caste'; for example, the workers who made shoes from the skin of dead animals came to be categorized as such. So was the case of several other occupations engaged in cleaning the drains, rowing the boats, washing dirty clothes, etc. In comparison, the people belonging to the first three classes: Brahmins, Kshatriyas, and Vaishyas came to be called __________ castes.",
          optionA: "High",
          optionB: "Middle",
          optionC: "Low",
          correctAnswer: "High",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Most of the worker-class people were included in the category of the Shudras. They were treated as inferior and unclean, and were also imposed several restrictions. In many cases, they were treated as __________.",
          optionA: "Scholars",
          optionB: "Outcastes",
          optionC: "Priests",
          correctAnswer: "Outcastes",
        },
        {
          question: "The above restrictions resulted in __________.",
          optionA: "Economic prosperity",
          optionB: "National unity",
          optionC: "Untouchability",
          correctAnswer: "Untouchability",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The society was fragmented into high and low castes. All people were not treated as equal members of the society. A divided society naturally lacked __________.",
          optionA: "Religious diversity",
          optionB: "National unity",
          optionC: "Economic prosperity",
          correctAnswer: "National unity",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Continuous wars depleted the population of the warrior class, but the low-caste people were not allowed to fight in the army. This weakened the __________.",
          optionA: "Economy",
          optionB: "Rulers",
          optionC: "Religious institutions",
          correctAnswer: "Rulers",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The need for caste reform became obvious because of the above causes. It was felt that the society could not progress if all people were not allowed to __________.",
          optionA: "Choose their caste",
          optionB: "Prosper",
          optionC: "Travel freely",
          correctAnswer: "Prosper",
        },
        {
          question:
            "As people from different regions were able to mingle owing to newer means of transport, they started to identify themselves as Indians. This led to an intense freedom movement.",
          optionA: "Economic prosperity",
          optionB: "Nationalism",
          optionC: "Untouchability",
          correctAnswer: "Nationalism",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3)
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "The caste system in ancient Hindu society was primarily based on occupation.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the medieval period, the caste system became more flexible and allowed individuals to choose their occupations freely.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Untouchability refers to the practice of not allowing low-caste people to come into contact with high-caste people.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Varna system in ancient Hindu society had four classes: Brahmins, Kshatriyas, Vaishyas, and Shudras.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The caste system led to a fragmented society and hindered national unity.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The caste system allowed individuals to freely choose their occupations without any restrictions.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The social reform movement in India during the medieval period had no impact on the caste system.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Continuous wars weakened the rulers but had no impact on the economy during the medieval period.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Ahoms, a tribe in India, retained their original language and customs despite settling in a new region.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The caste system in ancient Hindu society allowed individuals to freely change their Varnas based on their skills and preferences.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };

export var activityData;
